<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[TideSDK]]></title>
  <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-06-19T16:59:05-03:00</updated>
  <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[David Pratt (for TideSDK)]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[TideSDK Wiki Growing to Support Users and Developers]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/19/tidesdk-wiki-growing-to-support-users-and-developers/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-19T15:49:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/19/tidesdk-wiki-growing-to-support-users-and-developers</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our Wiki located at <a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki">https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki</a> continues to grow by leaps and bounds. We are receiving a lot of great information from the community and ask that you continue to share any valuable documents or media you may encounter concerning Titanium Desktop (the legacy SDK that TideSDK is growing upon). Much of this knowledge will live on through TideSDK to support our future users.</p>

<p>Join our mailing list to identify your find at</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups#!topic/tidesdk/B7k9KyVa3yg">https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups#!topic/tidesdk/B7k9KyVa3yg</a></p>

<p>or just let us know by chatting with us on IRC at #tidesdk on freenode.</p>

<p>Frankly, we want to set an example in our project for the level of documentation and support we will deliver to users and developers alike. Truly, we believe that high levels of documentation and community support will translate into more satisfied users and contributors to the project. We have some very good technology that will continue to improve.</p>

<p>While folks patiently await our first release candidate, we will continue to provide Titanium Desktop from our downloads area at</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/downloads">https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/downloads</a></p>

<p>When TideSDK is released, there will be no changes in the API. If you have no experience the Titanium Desktop and would like to get started on a Desktop app today, you can begin here (and transition to TideSDK as soon as we release it in the very near future).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marshall Culpepper Session Great Success]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/16/marshall-culpepper-session-great-success/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-16T20:29:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/16/marshall-culpepper-session-great-success</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our Friday session with Marshall Culpepper was to say the least &#8216;awesome&#8217;. We are very grateful to have his support for the TideSDK project. As you may be aware, Marshall was TiDesktop&#8217;s original developer and kroll was his &#8216;baby&#8217;. The session was well attended and our group benefitted immensely from Marshall&#8217;s insights.</p>

<p>Guiding the session using an outline prepared in advance, we gained from his knowledge of the past, discussed our present challenges, and looked toward the future. The session which ran a marathon 3+ hours, documented important legacy information, offered clarity concerning details of our project&#8217;s architecture, helped with issues around our drillbit testing framework, our development approach, library upgrades, packaging, distribution and much more.</p>

<p>The session ended with pledges to keep in touch along with a followup as we contemplate the challenges of Apple sandbox compliance. You will find a complete transcript of the session at:</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki/Q-&amp;-A-with-Marshall-Culpepper">Marshall Culpepper Q &amp; A Session</a></p>

<p>A big thank you Marshall on behalf of all involved in the TideSDK project.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Dive into TideSDK Architecture with Marshall Culpepper]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/deep-dive-into-tidesdk-architecture-with-marshall-culpepper/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-13T20:06:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/deep-dive-into-tidesdk-architecture-with-marshall-culpepper</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Join us for a scheduled Q &amp; A session with Marshall Culpepper, original developer of Titanium Desktop Friday June 15 at 3PM EDT / 1PM PDT on #tidesdk on freenode. We will be consulting on the architecture, potential, and priorities for TideSDK. In the interim, you can acquaint yourself with Marshall and his creation with the slideshare below. We are excited to have Marshall&#8217;s support and hope you are too.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.slideshare.net/marshall_law/titanium-desktop-intro">Titanium Desktop Intro - Marshall Culpepper Slideshare</a></p>

<p>More info is available at:</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/R5Q93i2aZqA">https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/R5Q93i2aZqA</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crowdsourcing Collection of Legacy Documents and Media]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/crowdsourcing-collection-of-legacy-documents-and-media/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-13T17:34:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/crowdsourcing-collection-of-legacy-documents-and-media</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since Appcelerator&#8217;s announced the discontinuation of Titanium Destkop, we have been  concerned about the potential loss and disappearance of valuable media, articles and knowledge that has accumulated over time about this great product.</p>

<p>We need your eyes and actions to help us gather valuable media, articles, tutorials, sample apps, slide presentations (slideshares) and any other valuable knowledge that may help future users of TideSDK.</p>

<p>Please post your findings on our Google group at:</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/B7k9KyVa3yg">TiDesktop Archive</a></p>

<p>I believe anyone involved in this effort will be surprised about the wealth of information floating around that we must collect up and preserve.</p>

<p>Please join in our crowdsourced effort.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Report 1 - June 10]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/10/progress-report-1-june-10/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-10T17:23:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/10/progress-report-1-june-10</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is first public post on progress. With the blessing of Boydlee, I have assumed the Project Lead position. You will find me at https://github.com/fairwinds. After some delay, TideSDK is moving forward in a positive way with the code and also with the full support of the initiative from Appcelerator through Kevin Whinnery.</p>

<p>I have sought commitments from Appcelerator for their support including specific legal, financial and technical assistance (when needed). I was happy this past week to have received this. I have been advised that Nina, Appcelerator&#8217;s dedicated legal support is working actively to immediately resolve the issue posed by the TiStudio (that impacted the TiDesktop and Kroll projects that we are inheriting). This has been a barrier to moving forward and a high priority request that I expect to see fulfilled shortly.</p>

<p>The short term plan is below. We are focusing here.</p>

<ul>
<li>Verify existing builds and build instructions on supported platforms. Tool chains need to be updated. Seek additional developer support once we have verified build processes to get people started easily.</li>
<li>Establish our CI capacity and automation.</li>
<li>Rename the core project in the code retaining the Ti namespace.
Ti === Titanium === TideSDK</li>
<li>Test and release a candidate at 1.2.1.RC1 that will be beginning of TideSDK line from Titanium Desktop inheritance</li>
<li>Update libraries incrementally that TideSDK relies upon (release frequently)</li>
<li>Create a branch for OSX sandboxing initiatives. (high priority)</li>
<li>Cherry pick priority bugs from JIRA and begin issue tracking process through Github which has a low barrier to use and where our project lives. JIRA will be used as resource only for historical context.</li>
</ul>


<p>First, welcome https://github.com/nazcasistemas to the development team who has already shown himself to be a dedicated team developer. We have dedicated long hours to ensure we are able to successfully build on all platforms (MacOSX, Windows and Linux). This is an important first milestone that we achieved recently and in a relatively short period of time between us. We have documented progress on a wiki at https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki. Josh has also been with us the past days giving us further insight into the code. Josh has also recently been successful on MacOSX Lion which is another important milestone and has been exploring Embedded Chromium for the project.</p>

<p>At this point, we are working through Drillbit tests to establish the quality of the builds and what may need some immediate attention.
Initially, we have a small developer group and we want to expand this shortly. As soon as we have verified, tested, and have documented our build instructions and laid the groundwork, we will begin soliciting more help from the community. We do not want a circumstance where help arrives and we are not prepared to get people going or fully understand our needs.</p>

<p>I have asked Appcelerator to transfer the TiDesktop and Kroll repos to us directly. This will retain all followers, forks, pull requests and such. I am hoping to have this happen immediately as we will be going through a process of renaming code components to rebrand. Rest assured the namespace will not change. That is Ti === Titanium === TideSDK so your projects should be unimpaired by what we are doing.</p>

<p>Sharry at https://github.com/molinto has pledged ongoing support on the communications and marketing side and we have in a short time identified priorities and taken stock of what we have. https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki/Communications-Strategy</p>

<p>The code base is very large and complex and requires a depth of understanding. For folks anxious to dig in the first step is a proper study of the code which is hosted at https://github.com/TideSDK. I am confident we will be able to extend our small team to meet the challenge.</p>

<p>In addition, we are working to determine builds on updated toolchains. There is currently a bug with scons that makes building on MSVC10 Express a problem. I am working on a bug fix to send on to the scons project when complete. Once this is fixed, we will be able to build using the current defacto compiler for Windows. That said, we already building on the older tools for Windows.</p>

<p>Next, we will be setting up automated build processes on a Continuous Integration (CI) system. I will be making my request to Kevin on server instances for various platforms to support the system. This is a critical need for the project as we must support 32 and 64 bit platforms and multiple operating systems. We must know what is happening at all times with the builds when there are changes to the code base.</p>

<p>This message is long and much more to say but out of time. Please follow our developments and we will keep appraised. Our objective is to release quickly and often. If our build processes and testing check out well and renaming exercise goes as expected, an early release should be available in the next week. Please stay tuned.</p>

<p>Regards,
David</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Happening? - 10th April]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/04/10/whats-happening-10th-april/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-10T16:49:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/04/10/whats-happening-10th-april</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi Everyone,</p>

<p>I know that many of you have been asking on the Google Transition group as to what is happening currently on the TideSDK (nee Titanium Desktop) front. Apologies for not being able to clearly state where we are at before, but I&#8217;m sure you can appreciate that there is a lot of things to take over from Appcelerator, and many decisions to be made regarding TideSDK moving forward.</p>

<p>Here&#8217;s the major points we are currently working on:</p>

<p>We&#8217;ve requested Jira Access and all the Q&amp;A data relating to Titanium Desktop from Appcelerator. Once we have this access/data, we will start filtering all the bug list in order of priority and we will be asking you, the community, to step forward and help us fix these issues.</p>

<p>The current branch of Titanium Desktop is available here https://github.com/TideSDK/titanium_desktop. Please feel free to fork this repo, and make bug fixes now in preparation for when we have the Jira data. We&#8217;ll be trying to keep the process of merging your changes as seamless as possible - that means simply you fork the code, make the change in your own repo, and create a pull request for us listing the Jira Bug ID and what you did to fix it. We don&#8217;t have the manpower to bug-test every single pull request, so we&#8217;ll be relying on the community to do that thoroughly during any release cycle.</p>

<p>About half of the team are currently investigating how to get the WebKit upgraded (particularly on Windows) as a matter of priority. If you want to help with this, please comment on this post and I&#8217;ll get you in touch with Burak and a couple of the guys who are leading that.</p>

<p>The rest of us are currently looking into building a prototype of how we see TideSDK evolving into a new product in the future. Basically, after looking through many, many options, this is revolving around the use of Chromeless, coupled with NodeJS. This is going well for a prototype investigation stage and we already have a sample application (just hanging off Webian, a sample Chromeless app), that:</p>

<ul>
<li>Runs the standard Chromeless CommonJS libraries</li>
<li>Runs a custom set of &#8220;Tide&#8221; CommonJS libraries</li>
<li>Runs a compiled version of node.js and executes a sample node.js script (called node.js which launches a HTTP server instance on port 8000 and returns some HTML)</li>
<li>Bundles a basic OSX package, whereby NodeJs and the application itself are executed by a bash script that I packaged up into an application file using another bash script - basically when we would build a &#8216;package&#8217; or &#8216;msi&#8217; for a user, we&#8217;re just running some scripts that bundle up our code, Xulrunner and a few other launch scripts together.</li>
</ul>


<p>We will, as a leadership group, be discussing this approach over the next couple of days with the intention of setting out a series of 0.1 release goals. These will be the features that will be available in our very first release, wich is going to be a very early alpha with a limited feature set, but it will be enough to provide a prototype. I will post those 0.1 release goals publicly once we have group agreement and push the code into a new GIT repo and ask the community to start providing feedback.</p>

<p>Looking forward to your comments over the coming days,</p>

<p>Boydlee</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logo Competition]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/23/logo-competition/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-23T15:50:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/23/logo-competition</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>A New Brand</h2>

<p>As we are starting afresh with the Titanium Desktop project, we need a few items to get us going. Firstly, the development team got together and decided on the ‘TideSDK’ (see minutes of the meeting here). The next step is on the agenda is the logo, this we be used in the application, on the website, any future mailings &amp; stationary.</p>

<p>What better place to get involved in a community driven project than designing a logo! The competition will run from 23 March 2012 00:01 to 23 April 2012 23:59, any submission between this time will be put to a public vote by the community on the 16th April 2012 &amp; from those results, a final three will be chosen. On the 25 April 2012 the development team will choose a winning entry! Please see the rules below:</p>

<h2>Terms &amp; conditions</h2>

<ul>
<li>The contest will run from 23 March 2012 00:01 (GMT) to 23 April 2012 23:59 (GMT)</li>
<li>By submitting an entry to the contest, you agree to the competition rules;

<ul>
<li>All submissions MUST be sent to admin[at]tidesdk[dot].org;</li>
<li>The competition is open to all;</li>
<li>Multiple submissions are encouraged;</li>
<li>Only 1 community/public vote allowed by IP address;</li>
<li>The design must be in a scalable vector format;</li>
<li>The development team will analyze the final 3 entries based on quality, design and overall community appeal;</li>
<li>The winner will be decided by the development team exclusively;</li>
<li>The judging period will be on 25 April 2012 (after the competition ends);</li>
<li>The winner be relinquish all rights of the design &amp; hand them over to the community project lead;</li>
<li>The winner will be notified by email &amp; public announced in the TideSDK blog;</li>
<li>All questions should be directed at admin[at]tidesdk[dot]org</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[20th March 2012 Minutes]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/20/20th-march-2012-minutes/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-20T16:33:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/20/20th-march-2012-minutes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Tide SDK Leadership Group Meeting</h2>

<p>2 dev teams: We are going to split into 2 development teams temporarily</p>

<ul>
<li>Team 1 will continue on with Ti Desktop, fixing bugs in the source code and trying to update WebKit for OSX/Mac to the new version (on the Ti Desktop repo currently under TideSDK Github, please ask Sharry for connection details)</li>
<li>Team 2 will look at the possibility of creating a new architecture based around a CommonJS/Chromium/Node solution. We will give this a set amount of discovery time before meeting again and discussing whether it’s both possible and feasible, and of course, whether based on our findings it is the right path forward. Russell – you and I can discuss offline what a reasonable time frame is as I don’t know your schedule but do know mine is currently manic.</li>
</ul>


<p>The split was basically along these lines:</p>

<ul>
<li>Team 1: Burak, Diogo, Piotr. Additionally, Dan and Sharry will start documenting and Sharry will continue on with the website maintenance and posting blog items, etc.</li>
<li><p>Team 2: Russell, Boydlee will look into the Node / CEF solution</p></li>
<li><p>Both: David would like to be across both teams. Dan and Sharry will also be across both teams where they can.</p></li>
<li>We’ll put the call out there on the website and the Google group for other devs to help out as well, but these will be the go-to people for questions regarding implementation and direction.</li>
</ul>


<p><a href="http://tidesdk.github.com/downloads/TideSDK-Minutes-20032012.pdf">Download Minutes PDF (~70K)</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leadership Team Survey Results]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/08/leadership-team-survey-results/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-08T15:29:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/08/leadership-team-survey-results</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Survey Results</h2>

<p>Here is the results of the survey - we collected 69 responses and they are quite interesting and varied. In particular, there seems to be 2 camps; those who want the product to be a sandboxed &#8220;web server&#8221; of sorts, able to run PHP, Ruby, etc, and those who prefer a JavaScript approach with the removal of these excess languages. From what I gather, it also seems a lot of people have no idea exactly what the existing capabilities of Ti Desktop already are.</p>

<h2>Download</h2>

<p><a href="http://tidesdk.github.com/downloads/SurveyMonkey-Survey-Results.pdf">Survey Results PDF</a> (~217K)</p>

<h2>The questions asked were:</h2>

<ol>
<li>A number of potential names have been put forward for the new &#8220;Titanium Desktop&#8221;. Below are some of the most popular suggestions. Pick one.</li>
<li>How important to you is the continued inclusion of server side languages (Python, Ruby, PHP)? If important, please explain why.</li>
<li>Would you prefer to see a more &#8220;javascript-based&#8221; approach to Ti Desktop, similar to that employed by the Titanium Mobile SDK?</li>
<li>Would you prefer to see WebKit replaced by Chrome Embedded (Chromium)?</li>
<li>What technologies do you want to see integrated into any future Ti Desktop product?</li>
<li>Would you like to see Ti Desktop become more extensible via the use of external, native modules?</li>
<li>What do you feel are the most important goals we shouldtry to achieve in the short term?</li>
<li>What do you feel are the most important goals we should try to achieve in the long term?</li>
<li>Please provide any more details regarding project direction, management, or anything at all that you want.</li>
</ol>


<h2>Visual Results</h2>

<p>A number of potential names have been put forward for the new &#8220;Titanium Desktop&#8221;. Pick one:</p>

<p><img src="http://tidesdk.github.com/images/survey1.png" alt="alt-text" /></p>

<p>How important to you is the continued inclusion of server side languages (Python, Ruby, PHP)? If important, please explain why.</p>

<p><img src="http://tidesdk.github.com/images/survey1.png" alt="alt-text" /></p>

<p>Would you prefer to see a more &#8220;javascript-based&#8221; approach to Ti Desktop, similar to that employed by the Titanium Mobile SDK?</p>

<p><img src="http://tidesdk.github.com/images/survey1.png" alt="alt-text" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[5th March 2012 Minutes]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/05/5th-march-2012-minutes/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-05T14:44:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/03/05/5th-march-2012-minutes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Tide SDK Leadership Group Meeting - Agenda</h2>

<h3>Project Name</h3>

<ul>
<li>Discussions were made around the name of the project, and the group. &#8220;Tide&#8221; was the clear winner from the survey of names suggested by the community. After some deliberation and decisions revolving around other similar project names on the web and how we could differentiate ourselves - plus a check on domain availability - it was decided and agreed by majority that the new name of the product and group would be called &#8220;Tide SDK&#8221;.</li>
<li>As agreed by the group, all correspondence and documentation will refer to the product by its full name of &#8220;Tide SDK&#8221;. In speech, conversation etc, this can also referred to as &#8220;Tide&#8221;.</li>
<li>Sharry Stowell purchased and is holding for the group the domains &#8220;tidesdk.org&#8221; and &#8220;tidesdk.com&#8221;. Our main domain will be the .ORG. The .COM will be redirected to the .ORG.</li>
<li>Our group logo will be created as part of our initial interaction with the community. We will open a competition for the best logo. Details TBC.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Website Development &amp; Community Co-ordinator</h3>

<ul>
<li>Sharry Stowell nominated. All seconded</li>
</ul>


<h3>Project Management Requirements</h3>

<ul>
<li>All code to be stored in a GitHub Open Source account. Sharry will organize this account.</li>
<li>Group decided on Atlassian, which includes project management plus Jira, etc. Used by a lot of open source groups. Sharry to organize - we will try to get a free account as we are an open source group.</li>
<li>OSQA decided upon as the open source Q&amp;A system, which is similar to Appcelerator&#8217;s and will hopefully ease the transition of existing Q&amp;A from that site to ours.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Server side languages &amp; Project Architecture</h3>

<ul>
<li>Group is divided on the continued inclusion or removal of SS languages.</li>
<li>The biggest bone of contention for not including them is that some developers rely on them for their current projects. According to Kevin, based on off-the-cuff knowledge, the amount of users actually using these packages is fairly small.</li>
<li>Alternatively, as a group most feel we do not have the capacity to support 4x languages - JavaScript, Python, PHP &amp; Ruby.</li>
<li>A suggested middle ground was keeping Python support only.</li>
<li>Another suggestion was that external language support (re: Python)
should be made as an extension and kept out of the product core.</li>
<li>Suggestions were made about the implementation of Node.JS as a core piece of the project. Node.JS would allow us to have a built-in framework for native extensions in C/C++, plus has a large community and a bunch of existing extensions we can leverage. It has a large set of built in API&#8217;s we wouldn&#8217;t have to rewrite (e.g. file system). It has a built
in package manager. Most of the group seems in favour of Node.JS with a bit of exploring.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Moving To Chromium (Chrome Embedded) or Keeping Webkit</h3>

<ul>
<li>Generally considered a good idea from an administration standpoint. The more bits we can &#8220;black box&#8221; then the more time we have to focus on core code.</li>
<li>As Kevin pointed out, one of Appcelerator&#8217;s biggest headaches wascontinually needing to upgrade and package the custom WebKit build with Titanium Desktop.</li>
<li>In saying, we need to first test Chrome Embed</li>
</ul>


<h3>Architecture Submissions</h3>

<ul>
<li>The group is divided along some lines of architecture, and the system as a whole needs to have some serious thought.</li>
<li>On that note, it was decided and agreed that everyone in the group who has firm ideas about architecture should document, with diagrams wherever possible, their ideas of how to architect the whole solution.</li>
<li>These submissions are to be made to the group and we will make further decisions based on them when we meet next.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Licencing</h3>

<ul>
<li>There is some licencing section of the Ti Studio licence that may interfere with the Apache licences that govern the rest of the existing Ti Desktop et al codebase.</li>
<li>David is to email the highlighted sections of the licence agreements in question to Boydlee and I will interface with Appcelerator directly to get them amended or get us an exception.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Date of the Next Meeting</h3>

<ul>
<li>Monday, 12th of March. 2012</li>
</ul>


<p><a href="http://tidesdk.github.com/downloads/TideSDK-Minutes-05032012.pdf">Download Minutes PDF (~70K)</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
