<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: blog | TideSDK]]></title>
  <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/categories/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-06-21T15:14:06-03:00</updated>
  <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[David Pratt (for TideSDK)]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unit Testing Progressing with Drillbit]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/21/unit-testing-progressing-with-drillbit/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-21T10:26:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/21/unit-testing-progressing-with-drillbit</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our team has been working to get Drillbit running and sucessfully passing unit tests. This is in anticipation of connecting to our Continuous Integration system late this week. After a commit to our repository, TideSDK gets built on a variety of operating systems and the unit tests will be executed. This will advise the team of the status of these builds at any time and also provide downloads at the current state.</p>

<p>There are a total of 4619 assertions made in the tests. Currently 85 tests are failing but this is already much better that where we started originally. We continue to progress. The unit test failures are primarily in the language and process modules.</p>

<p>The following is a screenshot of the unit testing and current status:</p>

<p><img src="http://tidesdk.github.com/images/drillbit-06212112.png" alt="June 21 Drillbit results" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[TideSDK Wiki Growing to Support Users and Developers]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/19/tidesdk-wiki-growing-to-support-users-and-developers/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-19T15:49:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/19/tidesdk-wiki-growing-to-support-users-and-developers</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our Wiki located at <a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki">https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki</a> continues to grow by leaps and bounds. We are receiving a lot of great information from the community and ask that you continue to share any valuable documents or media you may encounter concerning Titanium Desktop (the legacy SDK that TideSDK is growing upon). Much of this knowledge will live on through TideSDK to support our future users.</p>

<p>Join our mailing list to identify your find at</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups#!topic/tidesdk/B7k9KyVa3yg">https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups#!topic/tidesdk/B7k9KyVa3yg</a></p>

<p>or just let us know by chatting with us on IRC at #tidesdk on freenode.</p>

<p>Frankly, we want to set an example in our project for the level of documentation and support we will deliver to users and developers alike. Truly, we believe that high levels of documentation and community support will translate into more satisfied users and contributors to the project. We have some very good technology that will continue to improve.</p>

<p>While folks patiently await our first release candidate, we will continue to provide Titanium Desktop from our downloads area at</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/downloads">https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/downloads</a></p>

<p>When TideSDK is released, there will be no changes in the API. If you have no experience the Titanium Desktop and would like to get started on a Desktop app today, you can begin here (and transition to TideSDK as soon as we release it in the very near future).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marshall Culpepper Session Great Success]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/16/marshall-culpepper-session-great-success/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-16T20:29:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/16/marshall-culpepper-session-great-success</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our Friday session with Marshall Culpepper was to say the least 'awesome'. We are very grateful to have his support for the TideSDK project. As you may be aware, Marshall was TiDesktop's original developer and kroll was his 'baby'. The session was well attended and our group benefitted immensely from Marshall's insights.</p>

<p>Guiding the session using an outline prepared in advance, we gained from his knowledge of the past, discussed our present challenges, and looked toward the future. The session which ran a marathon 3+ hours, documented important legacy information, offered clarity concerning details of our project's architecture, helped with issues around our drillbit testing framework, our development approach, library upgrades, packaging, distribution and much more.</p>

<p>The session ended with pledges to keep in touch along with a followup as we contemplate the challenges of Apple sandbox compliance. You will find a complete transcript of the session at:</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki/Q-&amp;-A-with-Marshall-Culpepper">Marshall Culpepper Q &amp; A Session</a></p>

<p>A big thank you Marshall on behalf of all involved in the TideSDK project.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Dive into TideSDK Architecture with Marshall Culpepper]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/deep-dive-into-tidesdk-architecture-with-marshall-culpepper/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-13T20:06:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/deep-dive-into-tidesdk-architecture-with-marshall-culpepper</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Join us for a scheduled Q &amp; A session with Marshall Culpepper, original developer of Titanium Desktop Friday June 15 at 3PM EDT / 1PM PDT on #tidesdk on freenode. We will be consulting on the architecture, potential, and priorities for TideSDK. In the interim, you can acquaint yourself with Marshall and his creation with the slideshare below. We are excited to have Marshall's support and hope you are too.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.slideshare.net/marshall_law/titanium-desktop-intro">Titanium Desktop Intro - Marshall Culpepper Slideshare</a></p>

<p>More info is available at:</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/R5Q93i2aZqA">https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/R5Q93i2aZqA</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crowdsourcing Collection of Legacy Documents and Media]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/crowdsourcing-collection-of-legacy-documents-and-media/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-13T17:34:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/crowdsourcing-collection-of-legacy-documents-and-media</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since Appcelerator's announced the discontinuation of Titanium Destkop, we have been  concerned about the potential loss and disappearance of valuable media, articles and knowledge that has accumulated over time about this great product.</p>

<p>We need your eyes and actions to help us gather valuable media, articles, tutorials, sample apps, slide presentations (slideshares) and any other valuable knowledge that may help future users of TideSDK.</p>

<p>Please post your findings on our Google group at:</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/B7k9KyVa3yg">TiDesktop Archive</a></p>

<p>I believe anyone involved in this effort will be surprised about the wealth of information floating around that we must collect up and preserve.</p>

<p>Please join in our crowdsourced effort.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
