<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: blog | TideSDK]]></title>
  <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/categories/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-06-18T00:14:00-03:00</updated>
  <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[David Pratt (for TideSDK)]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marshall Culpepper Session Great Success]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/16/marshall-culpepper-session-great-success/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-16T20:29:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/16/marshall-culpepper-session-great-success</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Our Friday session with Marshall Culpepper was to say the least 'awesome'. We are very grateful to have his support for the TideSDK project. As you may be aware, Marshall was TiDesktop's original developer and kroll was his 'baby'. The session was well attended and our group benefitted immensely from Marshall's insights.</p>

<p>Guiding the session using an outline prepared in advance, we gained from his knowledge of the past, discussed our present challenges, and looked toward the future. The session which ran a marathon 3+ hours, documented important legacy information, offered clarity concerning details of our project's architecture, helped with issues around our drillbit testing framework, our development approach, library upgrades, packaging, distribution and much more.</p>

<p>The session ended with pledges to keep in touch along with a followup as we contemplate the challenges of Apple sandbox compliance. You will find a complete transcript of the session at:</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki/Q-&amp;-A-with-Marshall-Culpepper">Marshall Culpepper Q &amp; A Session</a></p>

<p>A big thank you Marshall on behalf of all involved in the TideSDK project.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Appcelerator Attempts to Clarify Support for Open Source TideSDK]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/14/appcelerator-attempts-to-clarify-support-for-open-source-tidesdk/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-14T20:49:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/14/appcelerator-attempts-to-clarify-support-for-open-source-tidesdk</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>The Bad News</h3>

<p>The TideSDK project received disappointing news today as Appcelerator attempted to clarify a position that left little in the way of support to enable the transition of the Titanium Desktop project to a community open source effort.</p>

<h3>The Original Pledge</h3>

<p>Appclerator originally pleged its support to this transition in its official blog</p>

<p><a href="http://developer.appcelerator.com/blog/2012/01/the-future-of-titanium-desktop.html">Official Appcelerator Blog - The Future of Titanium Desktop</a></p>

<h3>Appcelerator's Official Statement Received June 14</h3>

<p>From the Titanium Desktop Transition Mailing List</p>

<p>"Hi everybody,</p>

<p>Recently there has been some confusion around the legal status of the desktop codebase, and the official position of Appcelerator as it pertains to supporting the Tide SDK project.  I wanted to clarify both of those items, so that everyone knows where Appcelerator stands.</p>

<p>The source code located at https://github.com/appcelerator/titanium_desktop is open source under the terms of the Apache 2.0 license.  As such, it can be forked, modified and redistributed under the terms of the Apache 2.0 license, and is not covered or impacted by the licenses applied to other Appcelerator products, such as Titanium Studio.  However, "Appcelerator Titanium" and the Titanium Ribbon logo are registered trademarks of Appcelerator, Inc., and may not be used by Tide SDK or in any derivative works.</p>

<p>Appcelerator is focused on building our mobile platform, and our entire organization must be dedicated to that goal.  Thus, we cannot commit to any ongoing financial, administrative, or development support relationships. With that said, we do want to remain open to supporting this community on a case-by-case basis.  If there are specific requests that can be accommodated, we want to assist in those instances.  We would ask for those requests to be made of our developer relations team, which can be contacted via e-mail at community at appcelerator dot com.</p>

<p>Hopefully this helps clarify our original position.  Please direct any questions or concerns to community at appcelerator dot com.</p>

<p>Thanks,</p>

<p>-Kevin</p>

<p>--
Kevin Whinnery
Director of Developer Relations
Appcelerator, Inc."</p>

<p>Needless to say this was discouraging news after we felt that we had shored the necessary legal, finanical support and technical consultation we had received earlier from Kevin. You can follow this thread at:</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups#!topic/titanium-desktop-transition/IUe7S8lYNs0">Tiantium Desktop Transition List - Clarification on Appcelerator relationship</a></p>

<h3>Statment from Jeff Haynie, Appcelerator's CEO</h3>

<p>Jeff Haynie, Appcelerator's had intervened to advise the following:</p>

<p>Hey guys</p>

<p>I'm not sure how much more clear we need to be around the license for desktop. The code in github is Apache 2. However Studio is not. Studio is not the issue here. It's not OSS and never has been. It is however free. But studio is not required for desktop and shouldn't need to be considered as part of the TideSDK and likely would never be part of Studio anyway.</p>

<p>On the issue of packaging, our build server simply invoked the package scripts that are already available as part of the source and are open source. The wrapper code simply did work to add the build to our DB and some other Appcelerator cloud type stuff. It's is little less than 500 lines of code and wouldn't be useful if we did OSS it.</p>

<p>You have our moral and some limited financial support. I think that is reasonable.</p>

<h3>TideSDK Requests From Appcelerator</h3>

<p>Our requests for support were outlined in this document. Pledges of support from Appclerator's Kevin Whinnery came to us in an irc conversation on #tidesdk that was logged. The log is included.</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki/Appcelerator-requests">Appcelerator Requests</a></p>

<p>In total, our requests consisted of the modification a license clause in TiStudio, startup costs totalling $2104.00 and an ongoing monthly cost of $797.00. We requested assistance for some technical consultation for our developers for a limited time until as our developers become more familiar with the code base. Our budget is attached in the request document above for clarity and breakdown of the numbers. Mostly this is to provide for our Continous Integration (ci) system and to use those same servers in a role for user network packaging.</p>

<p>We had also asked that Appcelerator set aside funds that we could request on a case by case basis to offer bounties to accelerate important bug fixes and to encourage new developers into the code base.</p>

<p>Having felt we had received the commitments of support verbally, we were surprised the budget was rejected. We were advised to wait for Kevin's official statement on support. The official correspondence suggests no tangible support or cooperation. I had requested a face-to-face skype with Sandeep Johri to resolve this issue prior to Kevin making an official public statement on the mailing list. I have responded on the mailing list to clarify for all,  the figures and pledges made.</p>

<p>We are currently awaiting clarification from Jeff Haynie to understand the meaning of "minimal financial support". We deliverd a budget with that meaning in mind. For TideSDK to be developed, we must maintain a ci system to ensure we understand the impact of code changes on our builds and unit tests. We currently receive no funding from Appcelerator that I am aware of.</p>

<h3>A Lack of Support that is Difficult to Reconcile</h3>

<p>Appcelerator is currently ranked #2 by on momentumindex.com with 50.2 million in venture capital.</p>

<p><a href="http://momentumindex.com/100-open-source-companies-ranked-by-momentum-index">http://momentumindex.com/100-open-source-companies-ranked-by-momentum-index</a></p>

<p>This is a fact that is hard to reconcile with the rejection of our minimal request for legal, financial and technical consultation. Appcelerator dicontinued TiDesktop with a pledge to the community for a transition and continuation under a community effort.</p>

<p>Excerpt from the original pledge:</p>

<p>"The new Desktop project, which will undergo a name change from Titanium Desktop, will be governed and developed by the Desktop community, with material, administrative and logistical support from Appcelerator, but limited development resources. From the Appcelerator side, I will be acting as the liaison for this community to Appcelerator, and facilitate any action or assistance that needs to be rendered from our end."</p>

<h3>Summary</h3>

<p>Depite the current circumstances, this transition is occuring. There is dedicated and growing support for TideSDK. It is our desire for the TideSDK project to work together with Appcelerator on a collaborative and cooperative basis. That said we are not receiving the assistance that was pledged. We have requested a meeting to properly resolve this. It is desirable for this to end with the support we need together with a announcement of support from Appcelerator and a joint commitment towards the goals of a successful transition.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Dive into TideSDK Architecture with Marshall Culpepper]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/deep-dive-into-tidesdk-architecture-with-marshall-culpepper/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-13T20:06:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/deep-dive-into-tidesdk-architecture-with-marshall-culpepper</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Join us for a scheduled Q &amp; A session with Marshall Culpepper, original developer of Titanium Desktop Friday June 15 at 3PM EDT / 1PM PDT on #tidesdk on freenode. We will be consulting on the architecture, potential, and priorities for TideSDK. In the interim, you can acquaint yourself with Marshall and his creation with the slideshare below. We are excited to have Marshall's support and hope you are too.</p>

<p><a href="http://www.slideshare.net/marshall_law/titanium-desktop-intro">Titanium Desktop Intro - Marshall Culpepper Slideshare</a></p>

<p>More info is available at:</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/R5Q93i2aZqA">https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/R5Q93i2aZqA</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crowdsourcing Collection of Legacy Documents and Media]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/crowdsourcing-collection-of-legacy-documents-and-media/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-13T17:34:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/13/crowdsourcing-collection-of-legacy-documents-and-media</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since Appcelerator's announced the discontinuation of Titanium Destkop, we have been  concerned about the potential loss and disappearance of valuable media, articles and knowledge that has accumulated over time about this great product.</p>

<p>We need your eyes and actions to help us gather valuable media, articles, tutorials, sample apps, slide presentations (slideshares) and any other valuable knowledge that may help future users of TideSDK.</p>

<p>Please post your findings on our Google group at:</p>

<p><a href="https://groups.google.com/forum/?fromgroups&amp;hl=en#!topic/tidesdk/B7k9KyVa3yg">TiDesktop Archive</a></p>

<p>I believe anyone involved in this effort will be surprised about the wealth of information floating around that we must collect up and preserve.</p>

<p>Please join in our crowdsourced effort.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Report 1 - June 10]]></title>
    <link href="http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/10/progress-report-1-june-10/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-10T17:23:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://TideSDK.github.com/blog/2012/06/10/progress-report-1-june-10</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is first public post on progress. With the blessing of Boydlee, I have assumed the Project Lead position. You will find me at https://github.com/fairwinds. After some delay, TideSDK is moving forward in a positive way with the code and also with the full support of the initiative from Appcelerator through Kevin Whinnery.</p>

<p>I have sought commitments from Appcelerator for their support including specific legal, financial and technical assistance (when needed). I was happy this past week to have received this. I have been advised that Nina, Appcelerator's dedicated legal support is working actively to immediately resolve the issue posed by the TiStudio (that impacted the TiDesktop and Kroll projects that we are inheriting). This has been a barrier to moving forward and a high priority request that I expect to see fulfilled shortly.</p>

<p>The short term plan is below. We are focusing here.</p>

<ul>
<li>Verify existing builds and build instructions on supported platforms. Tool chains need to be updated. Seek additional developer support once we have verified build processes to get people started easily.</li>
<li>Establish our CI capacity and automation.</li>
<li>Rename the core project in the code retaining the Ti namespace.
Ti === Titanium === TideSDK</li>
<li>Test and release a candidate at 1.2.1.RC1 that will be beginning of TideSDK line from Titanium Desktop inheritance</li>
<li>Update libraries incrementally that TideSDK relies upon (release frequently)</li>
<li>Create a branch for OSX sandboxing initiatives. (high priority)</li>
<li>Cherry pick priority bugs from JIRA and begin issue tracking process through Github which has a low barrier to use and where our project lives. JIRA will be used as resource only for historical context.</li>
</ul>


<p>First, welcome https://github.com/nazcasistemas to the development team who has already shown himself to be a dedicated team developer. We have dedicated long hours to ensure we are able to successfully build on all platforms (MacOSX, Windows and Linux). This is an important first milestone that we achieved recently and in a relatively short period of time between us. We have documented progress on a wiki at https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki. Josh has also been with us the past days giving us further insight into the code. Josh has also recently been successful on MacOSX Lion which is another important milestone and has been exploring Embedded Chromium for the project.</p>

<p>At this point, we are working through Drillbit tests to establish the quality of the builds and what may need some immediate attention.
Initially, we have a small developer group and we want to expand this shortly. As soon as we have verified, tested, and have documented our build instructions and laid the groundwork, we will begin soliciting more help from the community. We do not want a circumstance where help arrives and we are not prepared to get people going or fully understand our needs.</p>

<p>I have asked Appcelerator to transfer the TiDesktop and Kroll repos to us directly. This will retain all followers, forks, pull requests and such. I am hoping to have this happen immediately as we will be going through a process of renaming code components to rebrand. Rest assured the namespace will not change. That is Ti === Titanium === TideSDK so your projects should be unimpaired by what we are doing.</p>

<p>Sharry at https://github.com/molinto has pledged ongoing support on the communications and marketing side and we have in a short time identified priorities and taken stock of what we have. https://github.com/TideSDK/TideSDK/wiki/Communications-Strategy</p>

<p>The code base is very large and complex and requires a depth of understanding. For folks anxious to dig in the first step is a proper study of the code which is hosted at https://github.com/TideSDK. I am confident we will be able to extend our small team to meet the challenge.</p>

<p>In addition, we are working to determine builds on updated toolchains. There is currently a bug with scons that makes building on MSVC10 Express a problem. I am working on a bug fix to send on to the scons project when complete. Once this is fixed, we will be able to build using the current defacto compiler for Windows. That said, we already building on the older tools for Windows.</p>

<p>Next, we will be setting up automated build processes on a Continuous Integration (CI) system. I will be making my request to Kevin on server instances for various platforms to support the system. This is a critical need for the project as we must support 32 and 64 bit platforms and multiple operating systems. We must know what is happening at all times with the builds when there are changes to the code base.</p>

<p>This message is long and much more to say but out of time. Please follow our developments and we will keep appraised. Our objective is to release quickly and often. If our build processes and testing check out well and renaming exercise goes as expected, an early release should be available in the next week. Please stay tuned.</p>

<p>Regards,
David</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
